Guide to the Edmond Pauker Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Business Files, 1898-1960; Series II; 14.6; (36 boxes)
  - CLIENT FILES
    - Chodorov, Edward
      - City Without Jews: contracts, 1933-35 (Box 19, Folder 385)
        For Chodorov's dramatization of the novel of this title by Hugo Bettauer
      - Common Ground: contracts, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 386)
      - Commotion Off Stage: contract, 1941 Feb 6 (Box 19, Folder 387)
        For Chodorov's dramatization of the story of this title by Vina and Eugene Delmar
      - Decision
        - Contracts, 1944-47 (Box 19, Folder 388)
          Incl: contract for screen adaptation by Ben Martin
        - Statements, 1952-58 (Box 19, Folder 389)
      - Hell on Wheels ( Saddle and Go ): copyright, 1956 Apr 3 (Box 19, Folder 390)
      - Honey: contract, 1933 Dec 18 (Box 19, Folder 391)
        For Chodorov's dramatization of the story of this title by Paul Gallico
      - The Hopkins Manuscript: contract, 1941 Mar 15 (Box 19, Folder 392)
        For Chodorov's dramatization of the novel of this title by R. C. Sherriff
      - The Irrational Knot
        Based on the novel by George Bernard Shaw
        - Contracts, 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 393)
        - Copyright, 1956 Oct 11 (Box 19, Folder 394)
        - Statements, 1956-57 (Box 19, Folder 395)
      - Josephus: contract, 1941 Sep 30 (Box 19, Folder 396)
        For Chodorov's dramatization of the novel of this title by Lion Feuchtwanger
      - Kind Lady
        Based on Hugh Walpole's story "The Silver Mask"
        - Contracts, 1932-57 (Box 19, Folder 397-398)
        - Statements, 1950-58 (Box 19, Folder 399-400)
        - Statements, 1950-58 (Box 20, Folder 401-402)
      - Listen To the Mocking Bird
        Based on the play, Tabitha, by Arnold Ridley and Mary Cathcart Borer
        - Contracts, 1957-58 (Box 20, Folder 403)
        - Copyright, 1958 May 5 (Box 20, Folder 404)
      - Monsieur Lautrec: contracts, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 405)
      - Oh, Men! Oh, Women!
        - Contracts, 1953-56 (Box 20, Folder 406-407)
        - Correspondence, 1953-56, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 408-416)
          Incl: Cheryl Crawford
        - Statements, 1954-56 (Box 20, Folder 417)
        - Programs, 1953-55, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 418)
        - Reviews and publicity, 1953-57 (Box 20, Folder 419)
          Incl: Four photographs
      - The Spa
        Based on the play, Olympia, by Ferenc Molnár
        - Contracts, 1956-57 (Box 20, Folder 420)
        - Copyright, 1956 Jul 16 (Box 20, Folder 421)
        - Statements, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 422)
      - Sunday Father: copyright, 1958 Jul 14 (Box 21, Folder 423)
      - Those Endearing Young Charms: contracts, 1943, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 424)
      - Villa on the Hill: contracts, 1940-42, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 425)
        Incl: contract with W. Somerset Maugham for Chodorov's dramatization of the story of this title by Maugham
    - Chodorov, Edward and H. S. Kraft
      - Last Judgement ( Cue for Passion ): contracts, 1940-41 (Box 21, Folder 426)
    - Chodorov, Jerome
      - Correspondence: general, 1951-54 (Box 21, Folder 427)
      - Power of Attorney, 1942 Jul 31 (Box 21, Folder 428)
    - Chodorov, Jerome and Joseph Fields
      - Junior Miss: contracts, n.d. 194? (Box 21, Folder 429)
      - Schoolhouse on the Lot: contract, 1938 Apr 5 (Box 21, Folder 430)
    - Cochrane, Albert F.
      - That's My Business: contract, 1943 Jan 18 (Box 21, Folder 431)
    - Cohen, Jack, David Levy, and E. L. Langman
      - In the Doghouse: contract, 1937 Sep 8 (Box 21, Folder 432)
    - Coleman, Martyn
      - How Now, Hecate?: contracts, 1945-47 (Box 21, Folder 433)
      - A Little for the Bottle: contracts, 1946-48 (Box 21, Folder 434)
    - Conners, Barry
      - The Patsy: contracts, 1930-36 (Box 21, Folder 435)
    - Courtney, Neil Cragin
      - Contract: general, 1941 Jan 24 (Box 21, Folder 436)
    - Crittenden-Long, Dillard and Arthur Sircom
      - Among Those Pleasant: contracts, 1940 Nov 2 (Box 21, Folder 437)
    - Crothers, Rachel
      - As Husbands Go: contracts, 1931 Jul 2 (Box 21, Folder 438)
    - Csoker, Franz Theodore
      - Dritter November 1918: contract, 1937 Jan 19 (Box 21, Folder 439)
        For adaptation by Ilse Lahn
    - Cullinan, Thomas Patrick
      - Contracts: general, 1952-58 (Box 21, Folder 440)
      - Correspondence: general, 1950-53 (Box 21, Folder 441-443)
      - Correspondence: general, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 444-445)
        Incl: photograph
      - Correspondence: general, 1955-56 (Box 21, Folder 446-447)
      - Road of Fear (formerly Traveling Man )
        - Contracts, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 448)
        - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 449)
        - Statements, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 450)
        - Publicity, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 451)
      - St. Columkille's Eve
        - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 452)
          Incl: Basil Sydney
        - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 453)
          Incl: Harald Bromley, Michael Redgrave, Basil Sydney
    - Dane, Essex
      - The Comeback: contracts, 1937 Feb 8 (Box 21, Folder 454)
    - Dawless, Smith and Esther Klinck
      - Uniforms by Schiaparelli: contracts, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 455)
    - Deval, Jacques
      - Soubrette: contracts, 1937-39 (Box 22, Folder 456)
    - Dickey, Paul and Charles W. Goddard
      - Broken Wing: contracts, 1929 Mar 22 (Box 22, Folder 457)
    - Doherty, Brian
      - Father Malachy's Miracle: contracts, 1938-39 (Box 22, Folder 458)
        Based on the novel of the same title by Bruce Marshall
    - Drégely, Gábor (Gabriel)
      - The House of Cards: contracts, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 459)
        Incl: contract for film treatment by H. S. Kraft
    - Dreiser, Theodore
      - An American Tragedy: contracts, 1931, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 460)
        For German production
    - Druce, Pawle, and Green
      Authors' full names: Jeannette Druce, Kathleen Pawle, and Howard J. Green
      - London Legend: contract, 1936 Sep 10 (Box 22, Folder 461)
    - Dunning, Philip
      - Night Hostess: contracts, 1934-35 (Box 22, Folder 462)
    - Dymow, Ossip
      - The Last Woman ( Die letzte Geliebte ): contracts, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 463)
      - Der Sänger seiner Trauer: contracts, 1930-39 (Box 22, Folder 464)
        Adapted by Josef Buloff and William Schack
    - Ebermayer, Erich
      - Professor Unrat: contracts, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 465)
        Based on the novel of the same title by Heinrich Mann
    - Ebermayer, Erich and Franz Cammerlohr
      - Cash ( Bares Geld ): contracts, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 466)
    - Eckersberg, Else
      - Three Years and One Night ( Drei Jahre und eine Nacht ): contracts, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 467)
    - Egyed, Zoltán de and Ilia Bródy
      - Aspirin: contracts, 1938 Mar (Box 22, Folder 468)
    - Ellis, Walter
      - Almost a Honeymoon ( On the Q.T. ): contracts, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 469)
    - Elman, Irving
      - Correspondence: general, 1953-56 (Box 22, Folder 470-472)
        Incl: Gustav Blum
      - Brass Ring
        - Contracts, 1950-53 (Box 22, Folder 473)
        - Statements, 1951, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 474)
      - The Darkness Below: contracts, 1950 Apr 18 (Box 22, Folder 475)
        For Elman's dramatization of the novel of this title by Frederic Morton
      - Tevye's Daughters
        Based on the book of the same title by Sholom Aleichem
        - Contracts, 1949-50 (Box 22, Folder 476)
        - Correspondence, 1950-53 (Box 22, Folder 477)
          Incl: Michael Ellis, Edward G. Robinson
        - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 478)
          Incl: Herman Levin
        - Statement, 1950 Sep 7 (Box 23, Folder 479)
      - "Varsity USA at The University of Virginia" (television screenplay)
        - Contracts, 1956 Apr (Box 23, Folder 480)
        - Statements, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 481)
    - Elman, Irving and Bernie Wayne
      - Lysistrata and Cyrano de Bergerac: contract, 1957 Jan 10 (Box 23, Folder 482)
    - Engel, Alexander and Alfred Grunwald
      - Dancing Partner ( Die Prinzessin und der Eintaenzer ): contracts, 1928-30 (Box 23, Folder 483)
    - Erskine, Chester
      - Correspondence: general, 1954-56, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 484)
      - Into Thin Air ( Or Not to Be )
        - Contracts, 1953-55 (Box 23, Folder 485)
        - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 486)
          Incl: Wally Cox, Herman Levin
        - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 487)
          Incl: Herbert Cobey
        - Correspondence, 1955-56 (Box 23, Folder 488-492)
          Incl: Hugh Beaumont, Ben Boyar, Garson Kanin, Loring Smith
        - Offering circular, 1954 Jun 15 (Box 23, Folder 493)
        - Financial statements, 1954-56, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 494)
        - Reviews and publicity, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 495)
    - Ery, Emery
      - Just For One Night ( Fuer eine Einzige Nacht ): contracts, 1938 May 30 (Box 23, Folder 496)
      - The Tattoed Woman ( Tetovált Nó ): contracts, 1940 Jul 10 (Box 23, Folder 497)
    - Essex, Harry J.
      - House of Ivory: contracts, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 498)
    - Essex, Harry J. and Harold Callen
      - "The Good Citizen" (story): contracts, 1942 July (Box 23, Folder 499)
    - Essex, Harry J. and Sid Schwartz
      - Fifth Estate: contract, 1940 June 12 (Box 23, Folder 500)
      - Prize Family: contracts, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 501)
    - Evans, Allen Roy
      - Contract: general, 1940 Oct 29 (Box 23, Folder 502)
    - Faragó, Alexander and László (Ladislaus) Aladár
      - Gruss aus Salzburg: contracts, 1931 Feb (Box 23, Folder 503)
    - Faragoh, Francis Edwards
      - Contract: general, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 504)
      - Pinwheel: correspondence, 1953-54 (Box 23, Folder 505)
        Incl: Sir Curtis Lampson
    - Farkas, Karl and Barre Dunbar
      - Night Without Tomorrow ( We Met In Lisbon ): contracts, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 506)
    - Fazekas, Imre
      - Altona: contracts, 1930 May 15 (Box 23, Folder 507)
    - Feld, Rose C. and George Ross
      - Sophie Halenczik, American: contracts, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 508)
    - Fields, Joseph and Irving Elman
      - The Honorable Picnic: contracts, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 509)
        For a play based on the novel of this title by Thomas Raucat
      - Mrs. Candy and Saturday Night
        Based on Robert Tallant's novel of the same title
        - Contracts, 1948-50 (Box 24, Folder 510)
        - Statements, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 511)
    - Flers, Robert de and Francis de Croisset
      - Les vignes du seigneur: contract, 1932 Nov 3 (Box 24, Folder 512)
        Adapted by Henry Baron
    - Finsterwald, Maxine and Lewis Fall
      - F. O. B.: contract, 1936 Sep 3 (Box 24, Folder 513)
    - Firner, Walter
      - Gesandtschaft von Astoria: contracts, 1938-39 (Box 24, Folder 514)
    - Fodor, Ladislaus
      - Contracts: general, 1931-42, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 515-516)
      - Affaire Caillaux: contract, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 517)
      - Bedtime Story: contract, 1935 Mar 21 (Box 24, Folder 518)
      - Birthday Gift: contracts, 1939 Jun 9 (Box 24, Folder 519)
      - A Churchmouse
        - Contracts, 1930-58 (Box 24, Folder 520)
        - Statement, 1953, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 521)
      - Dr. Juci Szabó: contracts, 1926-37 (Box 24, Folder 522)
        Incl: contracts with P. G. Wodehouse for his adaptation Good Morning Bill
      - The Fountain Pen ( A töltötoll ): contracts, 1933-40 (Box 24, Folder 523)
      - Head in the Noose: contract, 1931 Feb 16 (Box 24, Folder 524)
      - I Love an Actress ( Szeretek egy színésznöt ): contracts, 1930-31 (Box 24, Folder 525)
      - Jewel Robbery ( Ékszerrablás a Váci-utcában ): contracts, 1931-32 (Box 24, Folder 526)
      - Love Is Not So Simple: contracts, 1935-36 (Box 25, Folder 527)
      - Lullaby ( Bolcsodal ): contract, 1939 Oct 16 (Box 25, Folder 528)
        Contract with Edith Ellis for her adaptation entitled Why Keep a Diary?
      - The Red Pencil: contract, 1940 Dec 2 (Box 25, Folder 529)
      - "Summer is Near" (story): contract, 1941 Jul 25 (Box 25, Folder 530)
    - Fodor, Ladislaus and Hans Adler
      - Madame Lawyer I Love You ( Frau Doktor Ich liebe Sie ): contracts, 1937 Jul (Box 25, Folder 531)
    - Fodor, Ladislaus and Frederick Jackson
      - The Royal Box ( Die Hofloge ): contracts, 1935-39 (Box 25, Folder 532)
        Title varies
    - Földes, Emmerich
      - A kuruzsló: contracts, 1931 Oct (Box 25, Folder 533)
      - Paul Horvath Junior: contract, 1937 Feb 15 (Box 25, Folder 534)
        For adaptation by Arnold Korff and Cornel Wilde
    - Frank, Leonhard
      - Die Ursache: contracts, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 535)
    - Frank, Paul and Alfred Gruenwald
      - I am an American Girl: contract, 1941 Jul 23 (Box 25, Folder 536)
    - Frank, Paul and Ludwig Hirschfeld
      - Geschäft mit Amerika: contract, 1930 Mar 26 (Box 25, Folder 537)
    - Frank, Paul and Richard Reich
      - Gastspiel in London: contract, 1935 Jan 1 (Box 25, Folder 538)
    - Fraser, Georg
      - Nine Officers ( Neun Offiziere ): contract, 1936 Nov (Box 25, Folder 539)
    - Fulda, Ludwig
      - Der Dummkopf: contract, 1937 Mar 1 (Box 25, Folder 540)
        For adaptation by F. Milton Willis and Robert C. Fisher
      - The Pirate ( Der Seeraeuber )
        - Contracts, 1942-48 (Box 25, Folder 541)
          For adaptation by S. N. Behrman
        - Statements, 1954-58 (Box 25, Folder 542)
      - The Prodigal Daughter ( Die verlorene Tochter ): contracts, 1921, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 543)
    - Gábor, Andor
      - Paulchen: contract, 1930 Nov 7 (Box 25, Folder 544)
    - Gainfort, John H. C.
      - Contracts: general, 1937, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 545)
      - The Maker of Laws: contract, 1937 Nov 9 (Box 25, Folder 546)
      - Never No Third Degree: contracts, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 547)
      - Table for Four: contracts, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 548)
        Based on novel of the same title by Jack Iams
      - The Upward Trend: contracts, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 549)
      - The Wild Ass Stamps: contract, 1940 Mar 16 (Box 25, Folder 550)
    - Gainfort, John H. C. and Morris Zatz
      - The Great Adventures of Woodrow Wilson: contracts, 1938-39 (Box 25, Folder 551)
      - Mortal Gods: contract, 1938 Apr 6 (Box 25, Folder 552)
    - Gantt, Paul T.
      - And the King's Men: contract, 1941 Jun 19 (Box 25, Folder 553)
        Based on the play, The Pouter Pigeon, by Beulah Lyon
    - Gaumont, Irving and Irving Kaye Davis
      - Too Many Storks: contract, 1939 Dec 8 (Box 25, Folder 554)
    - Gaumont, Irving and Herbert C. Lewis
      - Time and Tide: contracts, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 555)
    - Gaumont, Irving and Jack Sobell
      - Thirty Days Hath September: contracts, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 556)
    - Gehri, Alfred
      - Le sixième étage: contracts, 1941, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 557)
    - Gerber, Eugene
      - L'assomption du citoyen Michel ( La résurrection du citoyen Michel ): contracts, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 558)
      - La révolte des veuves, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 559)
    - Gerber, G. A.
      - Genius in Love: contract, 1934 May 8 (Box 26, Folder 560)
    - Geyer, Siegfried
      - Candlelight ( Kleine Komoedie ): contracts, 1929-57 (Box 26, Folder 561)
        Adapted by P. G. Wodehouse
    - Glass, Ned
      - School Teacher: contracts, 1935-39 (Box 26, Folder 562)
        Incl: contracts for adaptation by Allen Boretz
    - Gordon, Hilda
      - Blind Man's Bluff (novel): contract, 1940 Apr 6 (Box 26, Folder 563)
    - Graham, Benjamin
      - True to the Marines: contract, 1934 Jun 11 (Box 26, Folder 564)
    - Granichstaedten, Bruno
      - Contracts: general, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 565)
    - Granichstaedten, Bruno and Hubert Marischka
      - Reklame: contracts, 1929 July 5 (Box 26, Folder 566)
    - Gredinger, Walter
      - "I Found Romance" (song): contract, 1940 Nov (Box 26, Folder 567)
        For collaboration with Albert Szirmai
    - Gruenwald, Alfred and Fritz Beda
      - The Blue Hour (originally entitled Ball At the Savoy ): contract, 1943 Jul 21 (Box 26, Folder 568)
        Adapted by Géza Herczeg and Alexander King
    - Guitry, Sacha
      - L'illusionniste: contracts, 1916-40 (Box 26, Folder 569)
    - Haggart, John
      - The Raven's Feather: contracts, 1946-47 (Box 26, Folder 570)
    - Halász, Imre
      - Happily Ever After: contract, 1936-37 (Box 26, Folder 571)
        Adapted by Alvin Kerr
    - Hammerstein, Oscar
      - Show Boat: contract, 1942 May 16 (Box 26, Folder 572)
        For Danish rights
    - Harbach, Otto
      - Roberta: contract, 1943 Mar 3 (Box 26, Folder 573)
        Music by Jerome Kern. Based on the novel by Alice Duer Miller
    - Harris, Pamela M.
      - A Place In the Sun: contracts, 1945-46 (Box 26, Folder 574)
    - Hasenclaver, Walter
      - Marriages are Made in Heaven ( Ehen werden im Himmel geschlossen ): contracts, 1935 Sep (Box 26, Folder 575)
        For adaptation by Rose Porter
      - Sinnenglueck und Seelenfrieden: contract, 1933-34 (Box 26, Folder 576)
    - Hatvany, Lili
      - Contracts: general, 1935-41 (Box 26, Folder 577)
      - First Love ( Erste Liebe ): contracts, 1931 Dec (Box 26, Folder 578)
      - Tonight or Never
        - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 579)
        - Review, 1939 Aug 8 (Box 26, Folder 580)
    - Hatvany, Lili and Francis DeWitt
      - On Such a Night: contract, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 581)
    - Hatvany, Lili and Sándor Hunyady
      - The Earl's Coronet ( Kilencágú korona ): contract, 1936 Jun 25 (Box 26, Folder 582)
    - Hatvany, Lili and Zoe Akins Rumbold
      - I Am Different: contracts, 1938-39 (Box 26, Folder 583)
        Incl: contract with Tallulah Bankhead
    - Haynes, Kenneth
      - Doomsday Book: contract, 1941 Feb 14 (Box 26, Folder 584)
        Dramatization of Leo Perutz's novel The Master of the Day of Judgement
    - Heilbut, Ivan
      - The Earth is Trembling ( Die Erdebebt ): contracts, 1942 Oct 2 (Box 26, Folder 585)
    - Hellman, Lillian
      - The Searching Wind: contract, 1944 Nov 29 (Box 26, Folder 586)
        In reference to Swedish rights
    - Heltai, Jenö
      - Death Sends for the Doctor ( Az orvos és a halál ): contracts, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 587)
        Incl: contract for adaptation by John H. C. Gainfort
      - Silent Knight ( A néma levente ): contracts, 1936, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 588)
    - Herczeg, Géza
      - I Made a Million (memoirs of Freddie Bartholomew): contract, 1947 Jan 16 (Box 26, Folder 589)
      - Limited to Nothing: contract, 1936 Sep 2 (Box 26, Folder 590)
      - "The Manicure Girl" (story): contract, 1934 Jun 10 (Box 26, Folder 591)
      - The Mirror: contract, 1940 Sep 24 (Box 26, Folder 592)
        For adaptation by Leyla Georgie
      - "One Thousand Dollars" (story): contract, 1935 Jan 10 (Box 26, Folder 593)
        Contract with George Haight to collaborate on the dramatization of Herczeg's story
      - Sentenced to Love and Death (book): contracts, 1940 Mar 27 (Box 26, Folder 594)
        By Harold E. and Elizabeth Rogers Dahl, edited by Géza Herczeg
      - Der Spiegel: contracts, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 595)
      - "The Story of a Cigarmaker (Life and Labor of Samuel Gompers)" (film treatment): contracts, 1940-44 (Box 26, Folder 596)
    - Herczeg, Oesterreicher, and Katscher
      Authors' full names: Géza Herczeg, Rudolf Oesterreicher, and Robert Katscher
      - Fregoli: contracts, 1942, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 597)
    - Herczeg, Géza and Leo Strauss
      - The Dancing Shylock: contracts, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 598)
        For adaptation by J. H. Neebe and Walter Craig entitled A Pound of Flesh
    - Holbrook, Walter and North Bigbee
      - Nearly Thirty: contracts, 1937 Feb (Box 27, Folder 599)
    - Horst, Julius and Wolfgang Pollaczek
      - The Red Flag ( Das rote Tuch ): contract, 1930 Jul 23 (Box 27, Folder 600)
    - Horwich, David
      - Husband, Dear Husband: contract, 1946 Mar 1 (Box 27, Folder 601)
    - Hunyady, Sándor
      - Contracts: general, 1935, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 602)
      - Black Steamed Cherries ( Fekete szárú cseresznye ): contracts, 1931-32 (Box 27, Folder 603)
      - Pusztai szél: contracts, 1931-32 (Box 27, Folder 604)
      - The Three Dragons ( A három sárkány ): contracts, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 605)
    - Impekoven, Anton and ---- Mathern
      - Max der Prominente: contracts, 1929-30 (Box 27, Folder 606)
    - Janney, Russell
      - "Breaker Girl" (story): contract, 1944 Mar 30 (Box 27, Folder 607)
        For adaptation by Herbert Clyde Lewis
      - Curtain Call (book)
        - Contracts, 1956-57 (Box 27, Folder 608)
        - Statements, 1956-58 (Box 27, Folder 609)
      - Miracle of the Bells (book)
        - Contracts, 1945-51 (Box 27, Folder 610)
        - Correspondence, 1946-53 (Box 27, Folder 611)
        - Statements, 1946-57 (Box 27, Folder 612)
      - So Long as Love Remembers (book)
        Formerly entitled Madonna of the Sword
        - Contracts, 1951, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 613)
        - Correspondence, 1951-54 (Box 27, Folder 614-617)
        - Statement, 1952 Apr 25 (Box 27, Folder 618)
        - Review and publicity, 1952-53 (Box 27, Folder 619)
      - The Velvet Kid (book)
        - Contract, 1957 Apr 12 (Box 27, Folder 620)
        - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 621)
      - The Vision of Red O'Shea (book): contract, 1949 Jul 26 (Box 27, Folder 622)
    - Jaray, Hans
      - Christiano Between Heaven and Hell: contracts, 1939, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 623)
    - Jeritza, Maria
      - Contracts: general, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 624)
    - Jerome, Helen
      - Pride and Prejudice: contracts, 1936-37 (Box 27, Folder 625)
    - Joachimson, Felix
      - Ugly Girl ( Das häsliche Mädchen ): contracts, 1930-31 (Box 28, Folder 626)
    - Johnson, Laurence E.
      - It's a Wise Child: contracts, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 627)
    - Johnson, Marion
      - Star Light, Star Bright: contract, 1944 Sep (Box 28, Folder 628)
    - Kádár, Endre
      - The Keyhole ( Kulcslyuk ): contracts, 1933-36 (Box 28, Folder 629)
        Incl: contract for adaptation by Lawrence Langner
    - Kadelburg, Gustav and Arthur Rebner
      With music by Hugo Hirsch
      - Die Tolle Lola (operetta): contracts, 1929-33 (Box 28, Folder 630)
    - Kaiser, Georg
      - The Great Fire in the Opera House ( Brandt im Opernhaus ): contracts, 1928, 1932 (Box 28, Folder 631)
      - Hellseherei: contract, 1929 Dec 18 (Box 28, Folder 632)
      - Zweimal Oliver: contracts, 1928-31 (Box 28, Folder 633)
    - Kálmán, Emmerich
      - Contracts: general, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 634)
      - Correspondence: general, 1952-53 (Box 28, Folder 635-637)
      - Miss Underground: contracts, 1943, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 638)
    - Kaufman, George Simon and Moss Hart
      - George Washington Slept Here: contract, 1942 Mar 17 (Box 28, Folder 639)
      - Merrily We Roll Along: contracts, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 640)
    - Kaunitz, Julius
      - Doctor Druse's Success: contract, 1934 Nov 8 (Box 28, Folder 641)
    - Kaus, Gina and Otto Edgar Eis
      - Schrift an der Wand: contracts, 1938-39 (Box 28, Folder 642)
        For adaptation by Lin S. Root
    - Kaus, Gina and Ladislaus Fodor
      - White Lady: contract, 1941 Jul 24 (Box 28, Folder 643)
    - Kaus, Gina and László Vadnai
      - Jean: contract, 1940 Dec 16 (Box 28, Folder 644)
        For adaptation by Joseph Lee Walsh
    - King, Arthur H., Jr.
      - Contract: general, 1958 Oct 9 (Box 28, Folder 645)
    - Kingsley, Sidney
      - Men in White: contracts, 1935-36 (Box 28, Folder 646)
    - Kohner, Frederick and Albert Mannheimer
      - The Bees and the Flowers (formerly entitled The Birds and the Bees )
        - Contracts, 1945-46 (Box 28, Folder 647)
        - Statements, 1946-59 (Box 28, Folder 648)
    - Konstantin, Leopoldine
      - Contract: general, 1935 May 29 (Box 28, Folder 649)
    - Körmendi, Ferenc
      - Forests of the Light: statement, 1951 Mar 29 (Box 28, Folder 650)